"lang"
{
	"Language" "english"
	"Tokens"
	{
		"INF_ITEM_1_TEXT" "Steel Breastplate"
		"INF_ITEM_2_TEXT" "Steel Helmet"
		"INF_ITEM_3_TEXT" "Crusader's Helmet"
		"INF_ITEM_4_TEXT" "Commander's Helmet"
		"INF_ITEM_5_TEXT" "Warrior's Blessing"
		"INF_ITEM_6_TEXT" "Ring of Five"
		"INF_ITEM_6_DESC" "Once wielded by a great sorcerer..."
		"INF_ITEM_7_TEXT" "Crystal forged necklace"
		"INF_ITEM_8_TEXT" "Rusty Shortsword"
		"INF_ITEM_9_TEXT" "Shortsword"
		"INF_ITEM_10_TEXT" "Stinger's Blade"
		"INF_ITEM_11_TEXT" "Shadowforged Longsword"
		"INF_ITEM_12_TEXT" "Commander's Highblade"
		"INF_ITEM_12_DESC" "A blessing from Lightfall itself..."
		"INF_ITEM_13_TEXT" "Short iron-axe"
		"INF_ITEM_14_TEXT" "Rusty Iron Bludgeonizer"
		"INF_ITEM_15_TEXT" "Heartbleed"
		"INF_ITEM_15_DESC" "The spikes hold memories of past victims..."
		"INF_ITEM_16_TEXT" "The Ravager"
		"INF_ITEM_17_TEXT" "Health Potion I"
		"INF_ITEM_17_DESC" "Restores 50 health."
		"INF_ITEM_18_TEXT" "Focus Potion I"
		"INF_ITEM_18_DESC" "Restores 25 focus."
		"INF_ITEM_19_TEXT" "Freshly Baked Bread"
		"INF_ITEM_19_DESC" "Restores 15 health."
		"INF_ITEM_20_TEXT" "Magnificent Berries"
		"INF_ITEM_20_DESC" "Restores 30 health."
		"INF_ITEM_21_TEXT" "Tome of Melee Strike I"
		"INF_ITEM_22_TEXT" "Tome of Melee Smash I"
		"INF_ITEM_23_TEXT" "Tome of Fireball I"
		"INF_ITEM_24_TEXT" "Tome of Arcane Blast I"
		"INF_ITEM_25_TEXT" "A brief introduction"
		"INF_ITEM_25_DESC" "Read me, if you dare..."
		"INF_ITEM_26_TEXT" "Wolf Pelt"
		"INF_ITEM_27_TEXT" "Wolf Meat"
		"INF_ITEM_28_TEXT" "A bag of flour"
		"INF_ITEM_29_TEXT" "Pumpkin"
		"INF_ITEM_30_TEXT" "Small Mushroom"
		"INF_ITEM_31_TEXT" "Ancient Book"
		"INF_ITEM_32_TEXT" "Ancient Book"
		"INF_ITEM_33_TEXT" "Aron's Belongings"
		"INF_ITEM_34_TEXT" "Smuggler's plans"
		"INF_ITEM_35_TEXT" "Mystics of the Wild"
		"INF_ITEM_35_DESC" "Heavy of knowledge, filled with secrets."
		"INF_ITEM_36_TEXT" "Tome of Healing Circle I"
		"INF_REP_1_NAME" "Lightfall"
		"INF_REP_1_DESC" "Lightfall has been the centre of Arngor since beginning of time, powerful people has risen and fallen."
		"INF_REP_2_NAME" "The Chantry"
		"INF_REP_2_DESC" "Their devotion for the holy lord has been spread through out Arngor, they believe the best in people and fight for justice, honor and prosperity."
		"INF_QUEST_1_TITLE" "A new journey"
		"INF_QUEST_1_DESC_SHORT" "Welcome to Arngor, traveler. Do you seek to enter our great kingdom? If so please report for duty at the mayor's chamber."
		"INF_QUEST_1_DESC_LONG" "Entering Arngor is currently restricted to trusted people only, great turmoil has infested itself upon our great kingdom. We do not seek to increase this instability by feeding our enemies more allies. Prove yourself and you will be allowed safe passage. Our mayor can be found in the upper floor of the local inn, Rorin is his name."
		"INF_QUEST_2_TITLE" "Wolf Pelts"
		"INF_QUEST_2_DESC_SHORT" "I really need some more leather scraps for my workshop, care to help me out?"
		"INF_QUEST_2_DESC_LONG" "I require 10 wolf pelts. I know right, wolves? You'll find them outside the castle roaming the forest, be careful though..."
		"INF_QUEST_3_TITLE" "Report for duty"
		"INF_QUEST_3_DESC_SHORT" "You seem like you're a capable fella, if you want to enter our kingdom you got to earn it! Report for duty at the bridge, find Commander Felix."
		"INF_QUEST_3_DESC_LONG" "I hope you aren't too rusty with weapons, either way you got to get your hands dirty, son. Meet up with Felix at the bridge, he'll give you further instructions!"
		"INF_QUEST_4_TITLE" "Explore the camp"
		"INF_QUEST_4_DESC_SHORT" "I bet you're eager to start? As you see, we've set up a perimeter here. A bunch of smugglers have overrun this part of the island, we don't have enough soldiers stationed here so you have to go check it out for us."
		"INF_QUEST_4_DESC_LONG" "This right here is a product of the growing turmoil in our kingdom, these smugglers are mining the excavation point. The cave can supply them with everything from weapons to magical artifacts, which is just what the enemy wants. This has to end, the enemy is getting closer to our very doorstep..."
		"INF_QUEST_4_OBJECTIVE_1" "Explore the mine"
		"INF_QUEST_4_OBJECTIVE_2" "Explore the main camp"
		"INF_QUEST_5_TITLE" "Strike the camp"
		"INF_QUEST_5_DESC_SHORT" "Awful, just awful... We have to free the slaves, but first we need to lower the number of mercenaries, slay a few of the scumbags."
		"INF_QUEST_5_DESC_LONG" "Slay 10 smugglers, watch out for their commanding officers, they may be too strong for you."
		"INF_QUEST_6_TITLE" "Liberate the slaves"
		"INF_QUEST_6_DESC_SHORT" "Great work so far! Now it is time for you to liberate the slaves, time is of the essence!"
		"INF_QUEST_6_DESC_LONG" "Rescue 5 slaves, bring them back home safely!"
		"INF_QUEST_7_TITLE" "A final assault"
		"INF_QUEST_7_DESC_SHORT" "It's time, young traveler. Your greatest challenge lies before you, gather some friends and take on the commanding officers. Crush the smugglers once and for all!"
		"INF_QUEST_7_DESC_LONG" "Neutralize the three commanding officers, one is located at the main camp, another is located in the cave and the last one can be found in the building just at the right from the bridge."
		"INF_QUEST_8_TITLE" "A new allegiance"
		"INF_QUEST_8_DESC_SHORT" "Outstanding, the smugglers have finally been crushed! Report back to Rorin, he will be most pleased."
		"INF_QUEST_8_DESC_LONG" "Rorin will reward you for your great bravery, traveler. Choose wisely! Best of luck, tread safely."
		"INF_QUEST_9_TITLE" "Food supplies"
		"INF_QUEST_9_DESC_SHORT" "Howdy stranger! Mind helping me out? I'm in dire need of certain supplies, I know that those damn smugglers got lots of supplies, care to fetch me some?"
		"INF_QUEST_9_DESC_LONG" "Fetch 6 supply bags from the smuggler camp and surrounding areas, be careful, the smugglers will not be happy!"
		"INF_QUEST_10_TITLE" "Wolf meat"
		"INF_QUEST_10_DESC_SHORT" "These darn wolves are everywhere! I need them gone, my farm is getting attacked regularly by those beasts. Slay some and fetch me their meat!"
		"INF_QUEST_10_DESC_LONG" "Fetch 10 pieces of wolf meat, the wolves can be found all over the island."
		"INF_QUEST_11_TITLE" "Potion Brewing"
		"INF_QUEST_11_DESC_SHORT" "Greetings traveler, would you mind helping us out? We need certain ingredients to brew important potions."
		"INF_QUEST_11_DESC_LONG" "The Chantry appreciates your help, please do fetch 5 pumpkins and 3 mushrooms. You can find these items in the forest, watch out for the wolves though. May the lord watch over you."
		"INF_QUEST_12_TITLE" "Regular Assault"
		"INF_QUEST_12_DESC_SHORT" "Felix told me you're good at getting your hands dirty, unfortunately the smugglers haven't abandoned the site just yet. We'll have to press harder and more regularly. Up for some action?"
		"INF_QUEST_12_DESC_LONG" "Kill some smugglers and obtain their secret battle plans. The more we interfere the greater the chance will be for us to savior!"
		"INF_QUEST_13_TITLE" "Logan's Secret"
		"INF_QUEST_13_DESC_SHORT" "Please, would you mind fetching some personal belongings of mine? An important book located in my room, in the house occupied by the smugglers."
		"INF_QUEST_13_DESC_LONG" "Go to the smuggler's camp, enter the building and fetch my book in the room to the left."
		"INF_QUEST_14_TITLE" "Wolves at the gate"
		"INF_QUEST_14_DESC_SHORT" "Hello, traveler! These darn wolves keep coming about, would you mind taking care of them?"
		"INF_QUEST_14_DESC_LONG" "Slay 10 wolves, you can find wolves all around the island, some more dangerous than others."
		"INF_QUEST_15_TITLE" "Aron's Box"
		"INF_QUEST_15_DESC_SHORT" "I have something important left behind at the building over at the smuggler's camp, would you mind fetching a pristine box from my room?"
		"INF_QUEST_15_DESC_LONG" "You can find the box in my room, at the right. Watch out for the smugglers, they aren't very fond of strangers..."
		"INF_QUEST_16_TITLE" "Smuggler's Might"
		"INF_QUEST_16_DESC_SHORT" "Hello again, traveler. Your services have been most useful! Yet, there is more to be done. A powerful legionnaire has arrived, bring some friends and face this new foe! The smugglers shall be crushed once again."
		"INF_QUEST_16_DESC_LONG" "The smugglers are quite hesitant to deploy reinforcements, a legionnaire has been sent to scare us. We shall not tremble before these mercenaries, bring some friends and face this new foe!"
		"INF_NPC_1_NAME" "Dock Master"
		"INF_NPC_1_GREETINGS" "Hello young traveler, welcome to the kingdom of Arngor!"
		"INF_NPC_1_DESC" "The island's dock master."
		"INF_NPC_2_NAME" "Fisherman"
		"INF_NPC_2_GREETINGS" "Why hello there! Far from home, eh? Don't mind me, I'm just trying to catch me some dinner."
		"INF_NPC_2_DESC" "A lone fisherman."
		"INF_NPC_2_Q_1" "What is this place?"
		"INF_NPC_2_A_1" "This my friend, is the capital outskirts. A small strategic island just outside the capital of Arngor. You may be allowed to travel there, if they find you worthy."
		"INF_NPC_2_Q_2" "Any rumors?"
		"INF_NPC_2_A_2" "Oh yes, smugglers have infiltrated the island... They have taken over the far end of the island, there's an abandoned mine there, probably what they're after... Mercenary scum!"
		"INF_NPC_3_NAME" "Mayor Rorin"
		"INF_NPC_3_GREETINGS" "Welcome, welcome! I hope you've found yourself at home. Are you ready for some action?"
		"INF_NPC_3_DESC" "An elected official of Lightfall, organizes the island."
		"INF_NPC_3_DIA_FIN" "Outstanding! I knew we could count on you, lad! You will be greatly rewarded for your services!"
		"INF_NPC_4_NAME" "Marcus Heinberg"
		"INF_NPC_4_GREETINGS" "Hello, stranger. Fancy earning some quick money?"
		"INF_NPC_4_DESC" "A local leatherworker."
		"INF_NPC_4_DIA_STA" "Any luck with the wolves?"
		"INF_NPC_4_DIA_FIN" "Hah! Great work, now I'll be up running in no time!"
		"INF_NPC_5_NAME" "Thor Heinberg"
		"INF_NPC_5_GREETINGS" "Greetings! Take a look at my wares, they're of the highest quality!"
		"INF_NPC_5_DESC" "A local blacksmith and weapons crafter, master Heinberg."
		"INF_NPC_6_NAME" "Mixos"
		"INF_NPC_6_GREETINGS" "Do you desire immense power? If you have the coin, I will provide..."
		"INF_NPC_6_DESC" "A mysterious jewelcrafter."
		"INF_NPC_7_NAME" "Commander Felix"
		"INF_NPC_7_GREETINGS" "Welcome to the island, stranger. Ready for some action?"
		"INF_NPC_7_DESC" "Chief Commander of the island."
		"INF_NPC_7_DIA_STA" "Any luck?"
		"INF_NPC_7_DIA_FIN" "Great work! Ready for more?"
		"INF_NPC_8_NAME" "Carl Parrington"
		"INF_NPC_8_GREETINGS" "Howdy, howdy! A fine day to help out an old farmer, eh? Assuming you don't have anything better to do?"
		"INF_NPC_8_DESC" "An old local farmer."
		"INF_NPC_8_DIA_STA" "How goes it so far?"
		"INF_NPC_8_DIA_FIN" "Thank you very much! I appreciate it."
		"INF_NPC_9_NAME" "Lord Warren"
		"INF_NPC_9_GREETINGS" "Good day my son, how has the lord treated you on this fine day?"
		"INF_NPC_9_DESC" "A holy disciple from the Chantry."
		"INF_NPC_9_DIA_STA" "Found the ingredients yet?"
		"INF_NPC_9_DIA_FIN" "Bless you, your courage will save many lives!"
		"INF_NPC_10_NAME" "Master Xavier"
		"INF_NPC_10_GREETINGS" "Greetings, all is well I assume?"
		"INF_NPC_10_DESC" "A master of combat tactics."
		"INF_NPC_10_DIA_STA" "Have you obliterated the smugglers yet?"
		"INF_NPC_10_DIA_FIN" "That'll teach them! Now we will know of their next moves, hah! Good work, lad!"
		"INF_NPC_11_NAME" "Master Combatant Ingor"
		"INF_NPC_11_GREETINGS" "Do you seek knowledge? My teachings will make you more powerful than ever!"
		"INF_NPC_11_DESC" "A master of melee combat."
		"INF_NPC_12_NAME" "Tallus the Wise"
		"INF_NPC_12_GREETINGS" "Magic is the true force of the universe, are you determined to learn? Feel free to browse my wares."
		"INF_NPC_12_DESC" "A master of magics."
		"INF_NPC_13_NAME" "Squire Logan"
		"INF_NPC_13_GREETINGS" "New to Arngor I suppose? Save yourself the trouble, there's nothing but turmoil left in the region."
		"INF_NPC_13_DESC" "A mysterious being."
		"INF_NPC_13_DIA_STA" "Found my book yet?"
		"INF_NPC_13_DIA_FIN" "Gratitude, now I can finally leave this place..."
		"INF_NPC_14_NAME" "Brewmaster Lopkins"
		"INF_NPC_14_GREETINGS" "Warm welcomes to you, traveler! Whatever you need, I'll provide!"
		"INF_NPC_14_DESC" "The tavern master..."
		"INF_NPC_15_NAME" "Hunter Avrius"
		"INF_NPC_15_GREETINGS" "You must be far from home, eh? Roaming these woods all by yourself. I suppose you're looking for work?"
		"INF_NPC_15_DESC" "A local hunter."
		"INF_NPC_15_DIA_STA" "Not having any trouble, are you?"
		"INF_NPC_15_DIA_FIN" "Great! Now we might be able to take a walk without getting ravaged."
		"INF_NPC_16_NAME" "Aron Perkley"
		"INF_NPC_16_GREETINGS" "A fine day for some beer, yeah? These smugglers have invaded our beloved island, hopefully someone will teach them a lesson!"
		"INF_NPC_16_DESC" "A local citizen."
		"INF_NPC_16_DIA_STA" "Did you find my box?"
		"INF_NPC_16_DIA_FIN" "Oh great, you found it, you really did! I can't thank you enough!"
		"INF_NPC_17_NAME" "Scout Johnson"
		"INF_NPC_17_GREETINGS" "Safe travels, friend. Watch out for the wolves."
		"INF_NPC_17_DESC" "A local scout."
		"INF_NPC_17_Q_1" "Why are you guys here?"
		"INF_NPC_17_A_1" "We're here to keep the wolves from getting any closer, we don't want them in our castle!"
		"INF_NPC_17_Q_2" "How did the smugglers get here?"
		"INF_NPC_17_A_2" "They got here from distant shores, from Arngor I suppose. Rorin thinks that they are affiliated with the Northeners..."
		"INF_NPC_17_Q_3" "Who are the Northeners?"
		"INF_NPC_17_A_3" "We have no idea, we've just been told that we have countless enemies to the North. For all I know it is a hoax, yet how would I know..."
		"INF_NPC_18_NAME" "Castle Guide"
		"INF_NPC_18_GREETINGS" "Welcome to Arngor and the capital outskirts! Lightfall is a few miles from here, over the sea. You can enter our kingdom when you have proven your loyalty!"
		"INF_NPC_18_DESC" "A humble local guide."
		"INF_NPC_18_Q_1" "Where do I go from here?"
		"INF_NPC_18_A_1" "Whatever you like, though you should speak with Rorin first. You can find him at the top floor in the inn."
		"INF_NPC_18_Q_2" "Why must I prove my loyalty?"
		"INF_NPC_18_A_2" "Our kingdom is in great turmoil, we cannot risk escalating the tension further. Therefore everyone who enters Arngor will have to prove themselves."
		"INF_NPC_19_NAME" "Slave"
		"INF_NPC_19_GREETINGS" "Are you here to free me?"
		"INF_NPC_19_DESC" "A slave, abused by the smugglers."
		"INF_NPC_19_Q_1" "You are free now!"
		"INF_NPC_19_A_1" "Thank you so much! May the lord bless you!"
		"INF_NPC_20_NAME" "Smuggler Lite"
		"INF_NPC_21_NAME" "Commanding Smuggler"
		"INF_NPC_22_NAME" "Young Wolf"
		"INF_NPC_23_NAME" "Elder Wolf"
		"INF_NPC_24_NAME" "Magnificent Wolf"
		"INF_NPC_25_NAME" "Guard"
		"INF_NPC_26_NAME" "Commanding Smuggler"
		"INF_NPC_27_NAME" "Commanding Smuggler"
		"INF_NPC_28_NAME" "Chef Pamsey"
		"INF_NPC_28_GREETINGS" "Howdy! How's the island treating ya?"
		"INF_NPC_28_DESC" "A local chef with surprising reputation."
		"INF_NPC_28_Q_1" "What do you cook?"
		"INF_NPC_28_A_1" "Anything, literally. As long as it is tasty!"
		"INF_NPC_28_Q_2" "Can I learn cooking?"
		"INF_NPC_28_A_2" "From me? Hell no! I'm busy enough as it is, maybe you will find something in the capital, if you gain entry."
		"INF_NPC_29_NAME" "Smuggler Legionnaire"
		"INF_NPC_30_NAME" "Commander Goran"
		"INF_NPC_30_GREETINGS" "Hail, traveler! I sense grave danger is at hand, you best be prepared to do your part, or else all will be lost..."
		"INF_NPC_30_DESC" "A young talented warrior, whose ambitions outlast the empire."
		"INF_NPC_30_Q_1" "What's going on?"
		"INF_NPC_30_A_1" "Darkness is ever rising, the catacombs have become affected by a dark curse. Lightfall has dispatched reinforcements to deal with this contamination. Soon we will have to face a threat greater than what we can possibly imagine..."
		"INF_NPC_30_Q_2" "Can we do anything to help?"
		"INF_NPC_30_A_2" "Yes, of course! We'll need all the manpower we can get a hold of. However the catacombs are sealed at this time, the doors have been sealed with magic. No one can enter until our magisters can figure out a spell to unlock these damn doors!"
		"INF_SPELL_1_TEXT" "Mortal Strike I"
		"INF_SPELL_1_DESC" "Strike your enemy with a deadly stab."
		"INF_SPELL_2_TEXT" "Crushing Blow I"
		"INF_SPELL_2_DESC" "Slam your foes with a powerful smash."
		"INF_SPELL_3_TEXT" "Arcane Blast I"
		"INF_SPELL_3_DESC" "Generates a blast dealing AOE damage."
		"INF_SPELL_4_TEXT" "Fireball I"
		"INF_SPELL_4_DESC" "Hurl a blazing bolt at your enemy."
		"INF_SPELL_5_TEXT" "Healing Circle I"
		"INF_SPELL_5_DESC" "Spawns a healing circle which will heal your allies!"
		"INF_NOTE_1_TEXT" "Welcome to Infestus"
		"INF_NOTE_1_DESC" "Hail, adventurer! Welcome to the world of Infestus! Please do feel at home, you should start off by going into the local inn. Start some quests and have fun! You have probably noticed the action bar at the bottom middle of the screen, this is where you put the spells you want to use, you can learn spells by buying tomes and using those tomes. When you have used the tome you will have a new spell in your spell panel, P by default. Drag and drop it into the action bar, if you drag it into the first entry you will have to press button '1' in order to activate that spell!"
		"INF_NOTE_2_TEXT" "The realm of Arngor"
		"INF_NOTE_2_DESC" "Turmoil has infested itself upon our great kingdom, light is no more. The brave soldiers of Lightfall brings forth a last stand against the rising evil in the North. Will we withstand what is to come? Our people are more divided than ever, we must unite if we are to defeat this evil. Keldroth has been overrun with the charred, Darkwood Forest will soon fall in the hands of the dark priestess. Soon she will march upon our great city, legends will become fact."
		"INF_NOTE_3_TEXT" "The Charred"
		"INF_NOTE_3_DESC" "A dark curse has reign its havoc on our people, sickness is spreading more rapidly than ever! The catacombs remain sealed, in fear or further contamination. If we do not cleanse this evil I fear that we will come to a bitter end!"
		"INF_NPC_30_Q_3" "I'm ready to enter the Catacombs!"
		"INF_NPC_31_NAME" "Sergeant Harold"
		"INF_QUEST_17_TITLE" "Foul Magic"
		"INF_QUEST_17_DESC_SHORT" "Wretched creatures have infiltrated the catacombs, I dare you to fetch some bone fragments off of our dead."
		"INF_QUEST_17_DESC_LONG" "These bone fragments might come in handy, perhaps we will be able to analyze the fragments in order to create an antidote against the foul magic used to turn our dead. Thirty fragments should be more than enough, however fetching them won't be easy..."
		"INF_NPC_31_GREETINGS" "There's much work to be done, travelers. The dark priestess has infested these tombs with dark creatures, may Lightfall strengthen your hearts!"
		"INF_NPC_31_DESC" "A young talented warrior, whose ambitions outlast the empire."
		"INF_REP_3_NAME" "Shadow Council"
		"INF_REP_3_DESC" "A vast group of powerful necromancers, empowered by the dark priestess herself. Together they have reign havoc on Arngor, smiting down enemies of all races."
		"INF_ITEM_37_TEXT" "Doomhammer"
		"INF_ITEM_37_DESC" "A deadly burden..."
		"INF_ITEM_38_TEXT" "Worn Battleaxe"
		"INF_ITEM_39_TEXT" "Sturdy Longbow"
		"INF_ITEM_40_TEXT" "Shield of Vengeance"
		"INF_ITEM_41_TEXT" "Forsaken Helmet"
		"INF_ITEM_41_DESC" "The carrier may experience psychosis..."
		"INF_NPC_32_NAME" "Demonic Rat"
		"INF_NPC_33_NAME" "Skeletal Ranger"
		"INF_NPC_34_NAME" "Moroes the Summoner"
		"INF_NPC_35_NAME" "Forgotten Guardian"
		"INF_SPELL_6_TEXT" "Crushing Blow II"
		"INF_SPELL_6_DESC" "Slam your foes with a powerful smash."
		"INF_SPELL_7_TEXT" "Taunt"
		"INF_SPELL_7_DESC" "Forces nearby enemies to attack you instead of your allies."
		"INF_SPELL_8_TEXT" "Shield Slam I"
		"INF_SPELL_8_DESC" "Strike your opponent with your shield, gaining extra threat in the act."
		"INF_SPELL_9_TEXT" "Shadow Circle I"
		"INF_SPELL_9_DESC" "Spawn a dark circle of shadows, your enemies will scream in agony."
		"INF_SPELL_10_TEXT" "Arcane Blast II"
		"INF_SPELL_10_DESC" "Generates a blast dealing AOE damage."
		"INF_CHEST_1_TITLE" "Moroes's Treasures"
		"INF_ITEM_42_TEXT" "Helm of Shadows"
		"INF_ITEM_42_DESC" "The mark of Keldroth has been engraved in its base."
		"INF_ITEM_43_TEXT" "Berserker's Helmet"
		"INF_ITEM_44_TEXT" "Wizard's Hat"
		"INF_ITEM_44_DESC" "But... I'm just Harry..."
		"INF_ITEM_45_TEXT" "Cursed Longbow"
		"INF_ITEM_46_TEXT" "Forgotten Bludgeonizer"
		"INF_ITEM_47_TEXT" "Scepter of Unholiness"
		"INF_ITEM_48_TEXT" "Axe of Defiance"
		"INF_ITEM_49_TEXT" "Health Potion II"
		"INF_ITEM_49_DESC" "Restores 100 health."
		"INF_ITEM_50_TEXT" "Focus Potion II"
		"INF_ITEM_50_DESC" "Restores 50 focus."
		"INF_ITEM_51_TEXT" "Hunter's Blessing"
		"INF_ITEM_52_TEXT" "Mage's Blessing"
		"INF_ITEM_53_TEXT" "Tome of Melee Smash II"
		"INF_ITEM_54_TEXT" "Tome of Shadow Circle I"
		"INF_ITEM_55_TEXT" "Tome of Taunt"
		"INF_ITEM_56_TEXT" "Tome of Arcane Blast II"
		"INF_ITEM_57_TEXT" "Iron Buckle I"
		"INF_ITEM_58_TEXT" "Iron Buckle II"
		"INF_ITEM_59_TEXT" "Forgotten Bulwark"
		"INF_ITEM_40_DESC" "Lightfall's reward for its bravest soldiers."
		"INF_ITEM_60_TEXT" "Shield of Brutality"
		"INF_ITEM_61_TEXT" "Wall of Torment"
		"INF_ITEM_62_TEXT" "Necklace of Necromancy"
		"INF_ITEM_63_TEXT" "Bandit's Buckler"
		"INF_ITEM_64_TEXT" "Bone Fragment"
		"INF_ITEM_65_TEXT" "Moroes's Signet Ring"
		"INF_NOTE_4_TEXT" "Infestation of Arngor"
		"INF_NOTE_4_DESC" "During the great war, a young woman fought for her right to the throne. Betrayed by her own people, she was cast away, banished... As she ventured through the lands of Darkwood, she discovered that she was not alone, an army would be built, a fierce army. Lightfall dispatched centurions to defeat the rebellion in the North, to prevent further bloodshed, she cursed herself and her followers. The dark priestess was born, and will come again, to reclaim what is hers..."
		"INF_SPELL_11_TEXT" "Healing Touch I"
		"INF_SPELL_11_DESC" "Replenishes your or an allys health."
		"INF_ITEM_66_TEXT" "Enforced Chestguard"
		"INF_ITEM_67_TEXT" "Wolf Steak"
		"INF_ITEM_67_DESC" "Restores 50 health."
		"INF_ITEM_68_TEXT" "Tome of Healing Touch I"
		"INF_ITEM_69_TEXT" "Necronomicon"
		"INF_QUEST_18_TITLE" "Saving Sergeant Harold"
		"INF_QUEST_18_DESC_SHORT" "One of our sergeants have been missing for weeks, we suspect he might have been captured by the savages that reside in the catacombs."
		"INF_QUEST_18_DESC_LONG" "Sergeant Harold was sent to inspect the catacombs after months of suspicion that something had gone bad down there, our priests didn't return when they should, some of them were sick, we couldn't risk letting them roam the outskirts freely so we threw them back in the catacombs for our own safety! We were desperate you see, but now I fear things have escalated further... If you find Harold, be sure to rescue him at any cost!"
		"INF_QUEST_18_OBJECTIVE_1" "Escort Harold safely to the surface"
		"INF_ITEM_70_TEXT" "Vial of Demonic Rat Blood"
		"INF_ITEM_70_DESC" "An essence of evil spires within..."
		"INF_NPC_36_NAME" "Servant of Keldroth"
		"INF_QUEST_19_TITLE" "Demonic Blood Samples"
		"INF_QUEST_19_DESC_SHORT" "I believe we can make use of some blood samples off of the rats that reside in the catacombs, would you care to help us out?"
		"INF_QUEST_19_DESC_LONG" "The Chantry is interested in studying the blood vial of these vicious beasts, these are no ordinary rats, they have been cursed by the dark priestess, we're sure of it! Their blood vial could prove useful in our campaign against the dark forces that seek to destroy us. Fetch me a vial of any rat's blood, but while you're at it, neutralize all of them!"
		"INF_ITEM_71_TEXT" "Rusty Key"
		"INF_ITEM_71_DESC" "Perhaps this key can be used to free Harold?"
		"INF_ITEM_72_TEXT" "Tome of Shield Slam I"
		"INF_NPC_37_NAME" "Skeletal Berserker"
		"INF_NPC_38_NAME" "Skeletal Avenger"
		"INF_NPC_39_NAME" "Skeletal Champion"
		"INF_QUEST_20_TITLE" "The Evil Within"
		"INF_QUEST_20_DESC_SHORT" "Young traveler, our greatest fear have come true! The island is no longer safe, our enemy has built an army right under our noses! We need you to neutralize this threat before it is too late!"
		"INF_QUEST_20_DESC_LONG" "For years the Capital Outskirts have protected the lands of Arngor from invaders, pirates and such... But now, I fear this position will be lost if we don't deal with the intruders that reside in the now opened catacombs, you will have to bring some allies shall you defeat the evil within. May Lightfall be with you! Slay them all!"
		"INF_QUEST_21_TITLE" "Moroes the Summoner"
		"INF_QUEST_21_DESC_SHORT" "A great foe of the Chantry is apparently the master mind behind this unfortunate infiltration of our island, we need you to defeat Moroes and his commanders. Should you be successful, the dark priestess herself would be weakened! Are you up for the challenge?"
		"INF_QUEST_21_DESC_LONG" "Moroes the Summoner, a powerful necromancer, once an archmage of Lightfall itself. Treacherous thoughts plagued Moroes, and eventually he was recruited by the priestess herself. His knowledge of the dark arts has made him as feared as Keldroth himself. Slaying him won't be easy, but if you bring enough people you should be able to put him out of his misery."
		"INF_NPC_40_NAME" "Skeletal Minion"
		"INF_ITEM_73_TEXT" "Broken Skull"
		"INF_ITEM_74_TEXT" "Token of Dread"
		"INF_ITEM_74_DESC" "This item surges of dark magic..."
		"INF_SPELL_12_TEXT" "Whirlwind I"
		"INF_SPELL_12_DESC" "Perform a full spin, attacking all surrounding enemies with lethal force!"
		"INF_ITEM_75_TEXT" "Wraps of the Brave"
		"INF_ITEM_76_TEXT" "Wraps of the Wise"
	}
}
